export const chapter = "Chapter - 8: I Slipped on a Banana Peel";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "What did the speaker slip on that caused them to hit their head?",
          optionA: "A patch of ice",
          optionB: "A roller skate",
          optionC: "A banana peel",
          correctAnswer: "A banana peel",
        },
        {
          question: "What did the speaker slip on that nearly killed them?",
          optionA: "A roller skate",
          optionB: "A patch of ice",
          optionC: "A bathtub",
          correctAnswer: "A patch of ice",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Where did the speaker land when they slipped inside the bathtub?",
          optionA: "On their head",
          optionB: "On their back",
          optionC: "On their face",
          correctAnswer: "On their face",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How many different places did the speaker slip in the text?",
          optionA: "4",
          optionB: "5",
          optionC: "6",
          correctAnswer: "5",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In which location did the speaker slip and tumble into space?",
          optionA: "Basement stairs",
          optionB: "Kitchen floor",
          optionC: "Bathtub",
          correctAnswer: "Basement stairs",
        },
        {
          question: "What does the speaker wear to prevent slipping now?",
          optionA: "Slippers",
          optionB: "Shoes or boots or clogs or flippers",
          optionC: "Socks",
          correctAnswer: "Shoes or boots or clogs or flippers",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the speaker's solution to avoid slipping?",
          optionA: "Avoid walking",
          optionB: "Wear socks",
          optionC: "Not wear slippers",
          correctAnswer: "Not wear slippers",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which line in the text suggests that the speaker had multiple slipping incidents?",
          optionA: "I slipped upon a roller skate",
          optionB: "I slipped inside the bathtub",
          optionC: "I slipped upon the basement stairs.",
          correctAnswer: "I slipped upon the basement stairs.",
        },
        {
          question: "What does the speaker wish regarding their slipping?",
          optionA: "They wish to slip more often.",
          optionB: "They wish they could stop slipping.",
          optionC: "They wish to slip intentionally.",
          correctAnswer: "They wish they could stop slipping.",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the common theme in the poem?",
          optionA: "Overcoming fears",
          optionB: "Conquering obstacles",
          optionC: "Repeated slipping accidents",
          correctAnswer: "Repeated slipping accidents",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "I slipped on a ____________ and fell and hit my head.",
          optionA: "banana peel",
          optionB: "roller skate",
          optionC: "patch of ice",
          correctAnswer: "banana peel",
        },
        {
          question:
            "I slipped upon a patch of ____________, which nearly killed me dead.",
          optionA: "banana peel",
          optionB: "roller skate",
          optionC: "ice",
          correctAnswer: "ice",
        },
        {
          question:
            "I slipped upon a roller skate and tumbled into ____________.",
          optionA: "space",
          optionB: "kitchen floor",
          optionC: "bathtub",
          correctAnswer: "space",
        },
        {
          question:
            "I slipped inside the ____________ and I landed on my face.",
          optionA: "basement stairs",
          optionB: "roller skate",
          optionC: "bathtub",
          correctAnswer: "bathtub",
        },
        {
          question: "I slipped upon the ____________ and on the kitchen floor.",
          optionA: "kitchen floor",
          optionB: "roller skate",
          optionC: "basement stairs",
          correctAnswer: "basement stairs",
        },
        {
          question:
            "So now I wear my socks and shoes or boots or clogs or ____________.",
          optionA: "flippers",
          optionB: "roller skates",
          optionC: "ice",
          correctAnswer: "flippers",
        },
        {
          question:
            "I guess if I don't want to slip, I shouldn't wear my ____________!",
          optionA: "slippers",
          optionB: "socks",
          optionC: "boots",
          correctAnswer: "slippers",
        },
        {
          question: "I slipped upon a ____________ and tumbled into space.",
          optionA: "bathtub",
          optionB: "roller skate",
          optionC: "patch of ice",
          correctAnswer: "roller skate",
        },
        {
          question:
            "I slipped on a banana peel and fell and hit my ____________.",
          optionA: "bathtub",
          optionB: "head",
          optionC: "space",
          correctAnswer: "head",
        },
        {
          question:
            "I wish that I could stop myself from ____________ anymore.",
          optionA: "rolling",
          optionB: "slipping",
          optionC: "tumbled",
          correctAnswer: "slipping",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "Slippery surfaces are responsible for accidents in the text.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "The speaker wishes they could continue slipping.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "The speaker wears slippers to prevent slipping.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The speaker tumbled into space when slipping on a banana peel.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Slipping incidents occurred in only one location in the text.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "The speaker slipped on a roller skate and hit their head.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "The speaker wishes they could stop slipping anymore.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The speaker's solution to avoid slipping is to wear socks.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Slippers are the best footwear to prevent slipping.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The common theme in the poem is about conquering obstacles.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
